[
    {
      "questionNo": "Q1",
      "question": "Farmer Joe is organising crates of apples. What is the face value of the digit 7 in the number 578?",
      "options": [
        "7",
        "70",
        "700",
        "0"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q2",
      "question": "Joe is labelling a crate with the number 605. What is the place value of the digit 5 in that number?",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "50",
        "500",
        "5,000"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q3",
      "question": "In another crate, Joe finds the number 842. What is the face value of the digit 4 in this number?",
      "options": [
        "40",
        "4",
        "400",
        "0"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q4",
      "question": "Joe labels a crate with the number 942. What is the place value of the digit 9 in this number?",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "90",
        "900",
        "0"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q5",
      "question": "Joe checks the number on a crate of apples and sees 732. What is the face value of the digit 2 in this number?",
      "options": [
        "20",
        "0",
        "200",
        "2"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q6",
      "question": "Farmer Joe is organising a crate with the number 453. What is the place value of the digit 3 in this number?",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "30",
        "300",
        "0"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q7",
      "question": "Joe labels another crate with the number 964. What is the face value of the digit 6 in this number?",
      "options": [
        "60",
        "600",
        "6",
        "0"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q8",
      "question": "Joe finds the number 217 on a crate. What is the place value of the digit 1 in this number?",
      "options": [
        "1",
        "10",
        "100",
        "0"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q9",
      "question": "As Farmer Joe sorts a crate with the number 385, what is the face value of the digit 8 in this number?",
      "options": [
        "0",
        "80",
        "800",
        "8"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q10",
      "question": "Joe organises a crate with the number 745. What is the place value of the digit 4 in this number?",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "40",
        "400",
        "0"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    }
  ]
  